Contact

Sarovara Towers Global Village Bangalore 7795571793 (Mobile)

www.linkedin.com/in/mujeebchoudhari (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

CAP

Product Development SAP Analytics Cloud

Certifications

SAP Certified Development Associate - SAP Extension Suite

SAP Certified Technology Associate
- SAP Fiori Implementation and
Configuration

Explore SAP Analytics Cloud - Record of Achievement

Scrum: The Basics

Honors-Awards

MasterMind

Hats Off

Hats Off

A-Team

Strategic Thinking

Mujeeb Choudhari

Chief Architect at Motiveminds

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Summary

2X SAP Certified Technology Consultant. My forte is Fiori, Fiori launchpad and security. I have extensively worked on ABAP, CDS, AMDP, SAC.

Over the period I have developed my skills in SAP BTP. Hands-on experience in building MTA application. Good exposure to SAP BTP services.

Good at SAP SD, MM and FI modules.

Expert in ABAP, CDS.

Experience

Motiveminds Consulting Pvt Ltd 5 years 6 months

Chief Architect September 2022 - Present (1 year) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

- Responsible for IP building and solution design

Solution Architect

March 2021 - September 2022 (1 year 7 months)

- -Responsible for conduct meetings with clients and management to determine project scope, budget, and timelines
- -Responsible for identifying business opportunities and converting them to projects.
- -Providing solutions
- -Team building and leading a team of 30+ developers
- -Product building
- -Trust building with clients

Project Lead

March 2018 - March 2021 (3 years 1 month)

ndia

- -Worked as a Project lead for different clients
- -Was handling team of 20+ member
- -Responsible for team building + directing the team during project work
- -Was responsible for delegating the work to appropriate team member
- -Was responsible for anticipating the potential roadblocks
- -Was responsible for ensuring project deadlines are met

Walmart Labs

Consultant

April 2017 - March 2018 (1 year)

Bengaluru Area, India

Incture Technologies

Senior Consultant

September 2016 - March 2017 (7 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Mindtree

4 years 1 month

Module Lead

January 2016 - September 2016 (9 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

- Was working as a Lead for a major FMCG's Distributor Management System implementation.

Senior Software Engineer

July 2014 - December 2015 (1 year 6 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

- Working as a developer for a major FMCG's Distributor Management System implementation.

Software Engineer

September 2012 - June 2014 (1 year 10 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Indian Institute of Technology, Bombay

Research Intern

April 2012 - September 2012 (6 months)

Mumbai Area, India

I have worked as Research intern in IITB on NVIDIA CUDA C programming

Education

Indian Institute of Technology, Bombay
Research Intern, Computer Science · (April 2012 - September 2012)

Walchand College of Engineering, Sangli B-Tech, IT · (2008 - 2012)